https://www.lidget.co.uk/terms-and-conditions/

Skip to content
Our BuildingsPent Roof Concrete GaragesPent Mansard Concrete GaragesApex Roof Concrete GaragesApex 15 Roof Concrete GaragesApex 20 Roof Concrete GaragesApex 90 Roof Concrete GaragesDouble GaragesLean To Sectional Concrete GaragesConcrete Sheds & WorkshopsConcrete Garden Buildings & Outdoor RoomsHighliner Concrete GaragesConcrete Battery GaragesDeluxe Concrete GaragesCustomisation OptionsHelp & ResourcesAboutPhoto GalleryTestimonialsPrivacy PolicyContact UsBrochure Request
Get Free Brochure & Price List » Request a FREE brochureGet a FREE online quotationFind your Lidget Compton AgentCall Free 01709 881844
Terms & Conditions
GET A QUOTE »
Lidget Compton > Terms & Conditions 1. InterpretationIn these Terms and Conditions the following expressions will have the followingmeanings unless inconsistent with anything specified in the Order Confirmationissued by Lidget Compton following receipt of your order:1.1 “Company”, “we”, “us“, “our” means Lidget Compton Ltd, Albion Drive, Thurnscoe, Rotherham, South YorkshireS63 0BA.1.2 “Customer”, “you”, “your” means the person or business placing anorder for Goods and whose order for the Goods is accepted by theCompany.1.3 “Distance Selling Regulations” means the Consumer Protection(Distance Selling) Regulations 2000.1.4 “Doorstep Selling Regulations” means the Cancellation of ContractsMade in a Consumer’s Home or Place of Work etc Regulations 2008.1.5 “Goods” means any Goods which we supply to you under these termsand conditions.1.6 “Site Preparation” means preparation of the site to provide a flat, level,concrete square base with an area, depth, strength and durabilityadequate to support the Goods in accordance with the Base InformationSheet provided by us.2. Site Preparation & Planning Approval2.1 You are responsible for Site Preparation prior to the Goods being deliveredand installed. We will not install the Goods on block paving, flagstonepaving or tarmac.2.2 You must obtain all relevant planning permissions, building regulationconsents and other necessary approvals at your own expense and riskbefore we can install the Goods. We may be able to guide you as towhether building consent is required and assist you with the applicationprocess if required.3. Delivery3.1 Delivery of the Goods shall be made to the address set out on your orderform.3.2 The price of the Goods shall include delivery to mainland England,Scotland and Wales (save for those areas specified in 3.3 below) and isvalid for a period of up to 6 months from the date on the order form, (or,where no date is shown on the order form, the order acknowledgementsent to you). In the event of a change in the VAT rate we reserve the rightto adjust the price accordingly.Delivery time is typically 3 to 4 weeks after receipt of the informationspecified in clause 3.4 for a standard size building.Delivery periods can vary according to season and all delivery times areestimates only and time of delivery will not be of the essence.3.3 Delivery to the Channel Islands, the Republic of Ireland, Northern Ireland,the Isle of Man, the Isle of Wight, BFPO (British Forces Post Offices) willincur an extra delivery charge.3.4 We will not advise you of a delivery date until:3.4.1 we have received cleared funds of the full balance of your order,except where trade credit has been specifically authorised;3.4.2 you have confirmed that the Site Preparation is complete;3.4.3 you have confirmed that the appropriate building approval/consent has been obtained or is not required; and3.4.4 you have returned your completed Help the Driver form.3.5 Upon receipt of the completed Help the Driver form we will confirmdelivery date with you one week before the anticipated delivery date. Thegoods will be delivered on an articulated lorry with a 13 metre (40ft)trailer. A smaller delivery vehicle is available if requested by you andconsidered suitable by us. You must advise us as soon as possible of anydifficulties that may arise on delivery including any difficulties in accessingthe site.There will be an additional charge for difficult and restricted accessdeliveries unless reasonable prior notice is given to us and the details arespecified on the Help the Driver form.3.6 We will not carry the Goods through a house or outbuildings to deliverand/or install them.3.7 In circumstances where access is restricted, we may deliver the Goods tothe nearest practical location to the delivery address rather than return theGoods to our depot and the Goods shall be at your risk following any suchdelivery.3.8 ”Delivery” for the purposes of these terms means delivery to a locationwithin approximately 23 metres (25 yards) from where we can park thedelivery lorry in order to access the site over reasonably flat and firmground.3.9 Any failed or abortive delivery of the Goods which are caused by you notproviding adequate access will attract a return delivery charge of up to£250.00. which is calculated as a proportion of the delivery cost.4. Installation by Us4.1 We will advise you by telephone or in writing of the date the Goods willbe installed which normally takes place within two working days of thedate of delivery of the goods. All installation times are estimates only.4.2 You do not need to be present while we install the Goods provided thatthe appropriate Site Preparation has been carried out and you haveprovided written confirmation of the positioning of the Goods.4.3 If your base is larger than the minimum size/dimensions advised to youby us for installation of the Goods, we require you to be present on site toadvise our installation team where you require the Goods to be installed,otherwise we will erect the building at our discretion.4.4 You will be responsible for the costs of re-siting the Goods if the base isnot prepared and laid with the correct dimensions and the installationteam are unable to install the Goods or you wish the Goods to berepositioned.4.5 We reserve the right to make an abortive visit charge of up to £250.00 if weare unable to install the Goods on the base because the Site Preparation isincomplete or defective or the site is not the correct size. The abortive visitcharge is calculated on the basis of the wasted time and travel incurred bythe installation team who are unable to install the Goods.4.6 After the building has been erected, Lidget Compton cannot be heldresponsible for water coming in under the panels or the door. A sand andcement fillet/timber weather bar should be fitted either by the companyor the customer, to help prevent water ingress.5. Risk and Property5.1 Risk in the Goods will pass to you once the Goods are delivered. Until youown the Goods, you must insure the Goods for their full value fromdelivery.5.2 Notwithstanding risk in the Goods passing when delivered, you will onlyown the Goods once you have paid us the full price of the Goods andinstallation, together with any other amount you may owe us for deliverycharges.6. Cancellation6.1 Under the Doorstep Selling Regulations if your order was placed during avisit by our Agent to your home you have the right to cancel your orderwithin 7 working days of placing your order, providing the Goods haven’tbeen delivered. Where you have agreed in writing for the Goods to bedelivered before the expiry of the 7 day cancellation period, you may nolonger have the right to cancel. Full details of your rights to cancel anddetails of how to do so are provided at the time of placing your order.6.2 Subject to 6.3 and 6.4, a cancellation charge of £250 will be payable in theevent of an order being cancelled three weeks or more after the date theorder was placed and more than 7 days before delivery. Orders cancelledless than 7 days before delivery will be subject to a further cancellationcharge equal to the additional costs incurred by us. These charges are toreimburse us for the abortive costs incurred in meeting your order.6.3 To the extent that the Distance Selling Regulations apply to your purchaseof the Goods, you have the right to cancel your order within 7 workingdays after the Goods are delivered providing the Goods have not beeninstalled.6.4 To exercise your right of cancellation, you must give written notice to usby letter or email quoting your Customer number and order number. Ifyou exercise your right of cancellation under the Distance SellingRegulations after the Goods have been delivered to you but not yetinstalled, you will be responsible for returning the Goods to us at your costto Lidget Compton, Albion Drive, Thurnscoe, Rotherham, SouthYorkshire S63 0BA. You should contact us if you want us to arrangehaulage, at your own expense, for the return of the Goods.6.5 You must take reasonable care of the Goods once you have exercised yourright to cancel under the Distance Selling Regulations. We will refund anysum paid by you or debited from your credit or debit card for the Goodswithin 30 days of cancellation, subject to receipt of the returned goods.7. General7.1 WE ARE NOT LIABLE FOR ANY DEATH, LOSS OR INJURY SUSTAINEDDURING OR AFTER THE DELIVERY OF OR INSTALLATION OF THEGOODS UNLESS SUCH DEATH, LOSS OR INJURY IS DUE TO OURNEGLIGENCE OR BREACH OF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS.7.2 If we or you choose not to rely on any of our or your rights under theseterms and conditions, this does not affect our or your liability to rely onthese same rights in future.7.3 Each clause of these terms & conditions is to be treated separately and theunenforceability of any single term or condition shall not affect theremaining terms and conditions, which shall remain in full force and effect.7.4 The Company provides a 10 year structural guarantee for the Goods fromthe date of purchase. We will provide you with details of this guaranteeupon request.7.5 We may assign this contract for the supply and installation of the Goodsbetween you and us at any time and may subcontract our responsibility forfulfilling any of our obligations under these terms and conditions at any time.7.6 No one else shall be able to enforce any of the terms set out in these termsand conditions.7.7 If we are unable to supply the Goods, we may offer substitute Goods butin this case we will only proceed with your order if you have consented tothe substitution prior to dispatch.7.7.1 We reserve the right at any time to make changes to thespecification of Goods. Changes which do not materiallyadversely alter the appearance, performance or quality of theGoods will not be notified prior to dispatch.7.8 Any notice required to be given under these terms and conditions shallbe in writing. You shall send any notice to Lidget Compton, AlbionDrive, Thurnscoe, Rotherham, South Yorkshire S63 0BA or byemail to sales@lidget.co.uk. We will send notices to the address which youhave provided on your order.7.9 The formation, existence, construction, performance, validity and allaspects whatsoever of these terms and conditions will be governed byEnglish law and any dispute in respect of the contract or any other matterarising in connection with it shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction ofthe Courts of England & Wales.7.10 You may have other rights granted to you by law in addition to those setout in these Terms and Conditions. These Terms and Conditions do notaffect those other rights granted by law.8. GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (EU2016/679)8.1 The personal information supplied by you on the order form will be usedfor internal record keeping to enable us to process your order.At Lidget Compton we take your privacy seriously. We will only use yourpersonal information to provide the products and services you have requestedfrom us. Lidget Compton will not share or sell your details to any businesses formarketing purposes.For full details on how we collect, process and store your personal details pleasesee our Privacy Policy.You are entitled to view, amend, or delete the personal information that we hold.If you wish to submit such a request please use the Personal Data Request Form here.If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you cancontact our Data Protection Officer who will investigate the matter.If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are processing your personaldata not in accordance with the law you can complain to the Information Commissioner’sOffice (ICO).Our Data Protection Officer can be contacted on marketing@lidget.co.ukor you can write to us at: Lidget Compton, Albion Drive, Thurnscoe,Rotherham, South Yorkshire S63 0BATerms & Conditions was last modified:
August 29th, 2018 by lidget.co.ukQUICK LINKSGet a FREE Online Quotation »Request Your FREE Brochure »Request a Callback » Find Your Lidget Compton Agent » Why Choose Lidget Compton »Need Some Help Choosing »Agent Login »OR GIVE US A CALL ON:
01709 881844
It Isn't a hard decision, we make the best concrete garages in the UK, our costs are rock solid, and if your garage is not still standing within 10 years, we'll rebuild it for you.That's the Lidget Compton GuaranteeTop TipSurveys show that most people would have a larger building than they originally specified once it is installed – a wider and/or longer building costs less if chosen when you first select – although you can extend buildings later, it is much more expensive.
CookiesThis site uses cookies to give you
a better experience. By using this site you are agreeing you are happy with this. Find out more.Yes, I am happy with this
